Ha. What do you mean, why?
There were studies that suggest
many who go into the performing arts...
(Beverley:)...suffer from an external locus
of identity.
(Penny:)Yeah, I don't know what that means.
(Beverley:)Well, it means you value yourself
only as others value you...
(Beverley:)...which is often the result
of unmet childhood emotional needs.
(Penny:)Oh, well, I had a wonderful childhood.
(Beverley:)Tell me about it.
(Penny:)I know my dad wanted a boy.
[SOBBING]
I... I just... I tried being good at sports,
but I hated getting dirty.
(Beverley:)And then, I'm assuming,
you entered adolescence.
(Penny:)Uh-huh. He called me slugger
until I got my first training bra...
(Penny:)...and then he just stopped
playing catch with me.
(Penny:)I wasn't slugger anymore.
(Penny:)Your mother's here.